<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>links_hackliberty_org on Lemmy Community Directory</title>
    <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/categories/links_hackliberty_org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in links_hackliberty_org on Lemmy Community Directory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://lemmies.blue42.net/categories/links_hackliberty_org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Agorism</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/agorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/agorism/</guid>
      <description>/c/Agorism on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/agorism
Description Agorism is the practice of counter-economics and the ideas associated with that practice. Agorist ideas assert that Libertarian philosophy occurs in practice, in the real world, as Counter-Economics. It was first proposed by libertarian philosopher Samuel Edward Konkin III in 1975.
Agorism (based on the principle of counter-economics) promotes withdrawing from the state and using counter-economic activities to minimize what a person contributes to the state in the form of taxes, license fees, and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/generative_ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/generative_ai/</guid>
      <description>/c/Artificial Intelligence on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/generative_ai
Description Generative artificial intelligence or generative AI is a type of artificial intelligence system capable of generating text, images, or other media in response to prompts. Generative models learn the patterns and structure of the input data, and then generate new content that is similar to the training data but with some degree of novelty.
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/bitcoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/bitcoin/</guid>
      <description>/c/Bitcoin on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/bitcoin
Description Bitcoin is an open source peer-to-peer system developed by Satoshi Nakamoto that aims to provide electronic cash. The system has no central server or trusted parties.[1] Bitcoin relies on cryptographic principles to create unique, unreproducible, and divisible tokens. Users hold the cryptographic keys to their own tokens and transact directly with each other, with the help of the network to check for double-spending
#### Rules</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conspiracy</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/conspiracy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/conspiracy/</guid>
      <description>/c/Conspiracy on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/conspiracy
Description In the law, a conspiracy refers to an agreement between two or more people to commit an unlawful act, or to deprive another person of his legal rights. The agreement to act must be moved toward a conclusion, whether or not it is actually accomplished. Plans made by a certain combination of people for unlawful or secret purposes may also be considered a conspiracy.
#### Rules</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Web</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/dark_web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/dark_web/</guid>
      <description>/c/Dark Web on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/dark_web
Description The dark web is a part of the internet where users can access websites without their identities being revealed and with their privacy protected by encryption offered by specialized web browsers like Tor. Since there are many levels of encryption, users can conduct various activities on the dark web that can be legal or illegal.
Broadly, the dark web refers to the unregulated part of the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encryption</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/encryption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/encryption/</guid>
      <description>/c/Encryption on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/encryption
Description In cryptography, encryption is the process of encoding information. This process converts the original representation of the information, known as plaintext, into an alternative form known as ciphertext. Ideally, only authorized parties can decipher a ciphertext back to plaintext and access the original information.
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flipper Zero</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/flipper_zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/flipper_zero/</guid>
      <description>/c/Flipper Zero on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/flipper_zero
Description Flipper Zero is a portable Tamagotchi-like multi-functional device developed for interaction with access control systems. The device is able to read, copy, and emulate radio-frequency (RFID) tags, radio remotes, iButton, and digital access keys, along with a GPIO interface.
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fringe</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/fringe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/fringe/</guid>
      <description>/c/Fringe on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/fringe
Description Exploring the very fringes of human knowledge and topics well outside cultural norms. ##### Topics may include:
- Paranormal
- Cryptids
- Ghosts
- Demons
- UFOs
- Aliens
- MILAB
- Orgonite
- Forbidden History
- Hollow Earth
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monero</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/monero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/monero/</guid>
      <description>/c/Monero on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/monero
Description Monero (XMR) is a decentralized cryptocurrency. It uses a public distributed ledger with privacy-enhancing technologies that obfuscate transactions to achieve anonymity and fungibility. Observers cannot decipher addresses trading monero, transaction amounts, address balances, or transaction histories.
The protocol is open source and based on CryptoNote, a concept described in a 2013 white paper authored by Nicolas van Saberhagen. The cryptography community used this concept to design Monero, and deployed its mainnet in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netsec</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/netsec/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/netsec/</guid>
      <description>/c/Netsec on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/netsec
Description netsec is a community-curated aggregator of technical information security content. Our mission is to extract signal from the noise — to provide value to security practitioners, students, researchers, and hackers everywhere. \u200e
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads. **Instant Ban.**
4. Stay on topic in a community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occult</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/occult/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/occult/</guid>
      <description>/c/Occult on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/occult
Description The word occult comes from the Latin word occultus (clandestine, hidden, secret), referring to “knowledge of the hidden” or “hidden knowledge”.
The term occult sciences was used in 16th-century Europe to refer to astrology, alchemy, and natural magic, which today are considered pseudosciences. The term occultism emerged in 19th-century France, amongst figures such as Antoine Court de Gébelin. It came to be associated with various French esoteric groups connected to Éliphas Lévi and Papus, and in 1875 was introduced into the English language by the esotericist Helena Blavatsky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>/c/Philosophy on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/philosophy
Description Philosophy (from Greek: φιλοσοφία, philosophia, &#39;love of wisdom&#39;) is the systematized study of general and fundamental questions, such as those about ***existence, reason, knowledge, values, mind, and language***.
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads. **Instant Ban.**
4. Stay on topic in a community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/privacy/</guid>
      <description>/c/Privacy on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/privacy
Description Privacy is the ability for an individual or group to seclude themselves or information about themselves, and thereby express themselves selectively. #### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads. **Instant Ban.**
4. Stay on topic in a community. Please reach out to an admin to create a new community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secret History</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/secret_history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/secret_history/</guid>
      <description>/c/Secret History on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/secret_history
Description A secret history (or shadow history) is a revisionist interpretation of either fictional or real history which is claimed to have been deliberately suppressed, forgotten, or ignored by established scholars. “Secret history” is also used to describe an alternative interpretation of documented facts which portrays a drastically different motivation or history from established historical events.
#### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyranny</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/tyranny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/tyranny/</guid>
      <description>/c/Tyranny on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/tyranny
Description #### Rules
1. Don&#39;t do unto others what you don&#39;t want done unto you.
2. No Porn, Gore, or NSFW content. **Instant Ban.**
3. No Spamming, Trolling or Unsolicited Ads. **Instant Ban.**
4. Stay on topic in a community. Please reach out to an admin to create a new community. Details * Subscribers 7 Posts 76 Comments 0 Daily Active Users 1 Weekly Active Users 1 Monthly Active Users 1 Published 2023-02-07 03:28:53 Updated 1969-12-31 19:00:00 Last Scraped 2023-06-16 11:06:13 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warriorship</title>
      <link>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/warriorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lemmies.blue42.net/community/links.hackliberty.org/warriorship/</guid>
      <description>/c/Warriorship on links.hackliberty.org https://links.hackliberty.org/c/warriorship
Description Protecting yourself is self-defense by the very definition of the term. Being a warrior means much more than being able to protect yourself. It means being willing and able to protect others as well as yourself. Warriors feel a sense of duty to protect those around them where the ordinary man only feels the need to protect himself. There is a big difference in the two.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
